<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyCityApp</string>
    <string name="city_reccomendations">City Recommendations</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="malls">Malls</string>
    <string name="tourist_laces">Tourist Places</string>
    <string name="restaurant_ogo">Restaurant Logo</string>
    <string name="parks_logo">Parks Logo</string>
    <string name="malls_logo">Malls Logo</string>
    <string name="tourist_places_logo">Tourist Places Logo</string>
    <string name="krishna_haveli">Krishna Haveli</string>
    <string name="sharda_dining">Sharda Dining</string>
    <string name="royal_darbar">Royal Darbar</string>
    <string name="tunday_kababi">Tunday Kababi</string>
    <string name="terai">Terai restaurant</string>
    <string name="bindas_dhaba">Bindas Dhaba</string>
    <string name="biryani_bay">Biryani Bay</string>
    <string name="rangrezza">Rangrezza</string>
    <string name="ambedkar_park">Ambedkar Park</string>
    <string name="vindyavasini_park">Vindyavasini Park</string>
    <string name="nehru_park">Nehru Park</string>
    <string name="city_mall">City Mall</string>
    <string name="orion_mall">Orion Mall</string>
    <string name="vishal_mega_mart">Vishal Mega Mart</string>
    <string name="v_mart">V Mart</string>
    <string name="trends">Trends</string>
    <string name="pantaloons">Pantaloons</string>
    <string name="gorakhnath_temple">Gorakhnath Temple</string>
    <string name="taramandal">Taramandal</string>
    <string name="ramgarh_taal">Ramgarh Taal</string>
    <string name="nauka_vihar">Nauka Vihar</string>
    <string name="budh_vihar_gate">Budh Vihar Gate</string>
    <string name="rail_museum">Rail Museum</string>

    <string name="restaurants_short_desc">Discover Gorakhpur\'s best spots for flavorful meals, from traditional thalis to iconic kebabs and trendy multi-cuisine eateries.</string>
    <string name="parks_short_desc">Relax and recharge in Gorakhpur\'s green spaces — ideal for morning walks, family outings, or peaceful time in nature.</string>
    <string name="malls_short_desc">Shop, eat, and unwind at Gorakhpur\'s popular malls — blending big brands, food courts, and fun hangout zones.</string>
    <string name="tourist_places_short_desc">Explore Gorakhpur\’s cultural gems — from sacred temples and museums to scenic lakes and boating adventures.</string>


    <!--  Restaurants  -->
    <string name="krishna_haveli_description"> Krishna Haveli is a charming vegetarian eatery that celebrates North Indian culinary traditions.With its warm sandstone décor, ornate mirrors, and gentle lighting, the ambiance feels like stepping into a family haveli. \n Its flagship offering is the North Indian thali—an array of perfectly spiced curries, fresh breads, fragrant rice, and seasonal veggies. Each dish is prepared without compromise on quality, capturing the soul of traditional cooking methods. \n The restaurant prides itself on serving meals in a timely yet relaxed manner. Ideal for both everyday meals and special family gatherings, the service is friendly and unobtrusive. \n Whether you\'re a strict vegetarian or simply someone who appreciates wholesome fare, Krishna Haveli offers a comforting and culturally immersive dining experience. </string>
    <string name="sharda_dining_description"> Sharda Dining is known for its no-frills, pure-vegetarian fare. Situated in a bustling neighborhood, it offers value-driven meals that draw everyone from students to families. \n Signature dishes include dal-bati-churma, chole-bhature, and seasonal sabzis, paired with piping hot rotis and fragrant rice. Portion sizes are generous, and you get wholesome, home-style cooking without high-end pricing. \n Cleanliness and hygiene are top priorities here. The open-kitchen setup makes it easy to see the preparation process, and the staff keeps the dining area well-kept even during peak hours. \n With bright, functional seating and quick service, Sharda Dining is more about satisfying hunger with reliability than indulgence—with no compromise on taste. </string>
    <string name="royal_darbar_description"> Step into Royal Darbar for a regal Mughlai dining experience right in town. The interior boasts plush chairs, ornate wall panels, and softly lit chandeliers—adding to the grand feeling. \n Their menu is a tribute to old-world Mughlai cuisine. Favorites include creamy butter chicken, rich rogan josh, and tender kebabs. Complemented with soft naans and fragrant pulao, every mouthful is a mini-royal feast. \n Service in Royal Darbar is polite and attentive. The staff guides diners through the menu and accommodates requests for spice levels or special combinations without hesitation. \n Perfect for celebratory meals or weekend indulgence, Royal Darbar brings fine-dining flair and rich flavors to your table—without breaking the bank. </string>
    <string name="tunday_kababi_description"> Tunday Kababi isn’t just a restaurant—it’s a slice of legendary culinary history. The tiny eatery is famous for galouti kebabs so tender they virtually melt on your tongue. \n These succulent kebabs are made with a secret blend of spices and slow-cooked to perfection—served in soft roomali rotis or with traditional parathas. Each bite ignites the classic flavors of Lucknow’s Awadhi cuisine. \n Lines often form outside during meal hours, but the wait is worth it. The experience is casual and vibrant, with patrons often enjoying live kebab flipping as they wait. \n Even today, the recipe remains true to its 100-year-old origin, making Tunday Kababi a must-visit for anyone seeking authenticity and culinary heritage. </string>
    <string name="terai_description"> Terai Restaurant blends local tastes with contemporary style, offering Indo-Chinese and North Indian options that cater to both youth and families. The interiors are neat, and the ambiance is casual and welcoming. \n Their chowmein and paneer dishes are popular, while weekend specials often include spicy gravies and unique tandoori options. \n Ideal for group hangouts, the pricing is moderate, and service is quick. It strikes a perfect balance between taste, affordability, and casual comfort. \n Whether it’s lunch after shopping or an informal birthday dinner, Terai delivers satisfaction in a friendly setting. </string>
    <string name="bindas_dhaba_description"> Bindas Dhaba brings rustic Punjabi vibes into an urban setting. From the décor—think wooden benches and colorful wall art—to the food, everything echoes the energy of a roadside dhaba. \n Their butter chicken, dal makhani, and stuffed parathas are packed with bold spices and rich flavors. Served with a side of onion salad and lassi, the meals feel complete. \n The open-air section and lively Bollywood music complete the roadside-eating experience. \n It’s a perfect weekend spot to go with friends when you\'re craving bold flavors and a fun atmosphere. </string>
    <string name="biryani_bay_description"> Biryani Bay specializes in regional rice delicacies, particularly Hyderabadi and Lucknowi biryanis. The aroma alone will pull you in as saffron, ghee, and spices mix in the air. \n They offer chicken, mutton, egg, and veg biryani with raita and mirchi salan on the side. Each dish is layered with flavor and cooked in traditional dum\-style. \n The interior is small but neat, with take-away options equally popular among regulars. \n If you’re short on time but don’t want to compromise on taste, Biryani Bay makes for a great quick-stop biryani destination. </string>
    <string name="rangrezza_description"> Rangrezza lives up to its name with vibrant interiors and a multi-cuisine menu that spans Indian, Chinese, and continental. Its décor is colorful and eclectic, making it a favorite among young diners. \n From chili paneer to pasta arrabiata and biryani to butter naan, the variety ensures everyone finds something. \n The service is quick, and portion sizes are generous, making it good value for money. \n Rangrezza is an ideal place for celebrations, casual meals, or just trying a bit of everything on one plate. </string>
    <!--  Parks  -->
    <string name="ambedkar_park_description"> Ambedkar Park is both a vibrant public green space and a moving tribute to Dr. B.R. Ambedkar. Its architecture is grand, with majestic sandstone pillars, statues, and calm water features that complement the landscaped gardens. \n The park\'s sprawling lawns and walkways are ideal for early morning walkers, families, and visitors seeking quietude. Fountains activate in the evening, creating a relaxing ambiance. \n The park hosts occasional cultural events and fairs, adding to its communal warmth. Flower beds, manicured shrubs, and shaded benches make it excellent for reading or people-watching. \n Visiting Ambedkar Park offers both visual and emotional enrichment—honoring a revered leader while providing a restful retreat from the urban rush. </string>
    <string name="vindyavasini_park_description"> Tucked in the suburban neighborhood, Vindyavasini Park is a soothing retreat bathed in greenery. Its winding paths are perfect for gentle morning walks or light jogging. \n The park is sprinkled with benches and seating areas under shade, ideal for reading or leisurely conversation. You\'ll often hear the sounds of birds, adding to the tranquil setting. \n Floral arrangements and seasonal plantings bring bursts of color, and the landscaping feels intentional yet relaxed. It’s a community favorite for sunset viewing or post-school family time. \n While compact, Vindyavasini Park offers a peaceful oasis and functions as a communal heart for nearby residents. </string>
    <string name="nehru_park_description"> Named after Jawaharlal Nehru, this park balances structured design with communal warmth. Wide grassy lawns invite families to picnic, children to run free, and pets to roam. \n A dedicated play area with swings, slides, and safety surfacing keeps younger visitors entertained. The greenery here is mature, with large shade trees that protect against the afternoon sun. \n Open spaces are often used for small events or yoga classes, and seating pavilions offer relaxed vantage points. The park’s layout seamlessly supports both energetic and peaceful activities. \n Whether you\'re in search of a playful afternoon or a silent corner to unwind, Nehru Park adapts effortlessly to your mood. </string>
    <!--  Malls  -->
    <string name="city_mall_description"> City Mall caters to a diverse set of urban needs—fashion, food, and entertainment—under one roof. Shoppers will find both national and local brands, along with boutiques for niche fashion. \n A multi-cuisine food court serves everything from fast food to regional specialties, while a multiplex screens the latest movies. Casual seating spaces are placed throughout for rest and meetups. \n The mall hosts regular sales, pop-up stores, and events like book fairs or cultural programs, giving the space a community character beyond just retail. \n Wide corridors, modern lighting, and interactive info kiosks keep it feeling fresh and customer-centric—a lively urban hub for shoppers and diners alike. </string>
    <string name="orion_mall_description"> Orion Mall stands out for its sleek modern architecture and well-thought-out layout. Clean lines, open atriums, and natural lighting make it feel spacious and welcoming. \n High-end fashion, electronics, and lifestyle stores fill its corridors, alongside an entertainment zone featuring a gaming arcade and play area for kids. \n Cafes and restaurants are arranged in open clusters, ideal for casual meetups and extended family meals. Frequent events and exhibitions add to its urban-destination appeal. \n Altogether, Orion Mall offers style, variety, and convenience—combined into one contemporary shopping ecosystem. </string>
    <string name="vishal_mega_mart_description"> Vishal Mega Mart is perfect for budget-conscious shoppers seeking variety. From ready-to-wear clothing to groceries and household essentials, it covers daily needs under one roof. \n The atmosphere is utilitarian—wide aisles, clear signboards, and accessible shelving. You\'ll find both fresh and packaged goods, along with an expanding private-label collection. \n Periodic discounts and value combos make it a favorite with local families who prioritize price over premium branding. \n Despite its straightforward setup, its utility and low prices make Vishal Mega Mart a reliable anchor in the local retail mix. </string>
    <string name="v_mart_description"> V Mart is a customer-friendly value retailer offering fashion and household items at affordable prices. The store layout is clean and sections are categorized neatly—women, men, kids, and home essentials. \n Clothing items are trendy yet economical, and footwear, kitchenware, and basic linens are easy to find. The store looks balanced—not too premium, not too scruffy. \n Frequent offers and festival deals enhance its appeal. Service staff maintain ready-to-wear racks, assist with sizes, and keep a cheerful tone. \n For families looking to accomplish all shopping needs with good value and minimal hassle, V Mart hits the mark. </string>
    <string name="trends_description"> Reliance Trends is your mid-range fashion destination, offering the latest in styles for all ages. The store is brightly lit, organized by seasonal themes—like “spring collection” or “back to college.” \n Brands range from ethnic chic to casual denim, and the kids’ section features small fashion trends, making it an all-in-one shopping spot. \n Frequent store-wide sales attract weekend crowds, and well-trained staff help with fittings, mix‑and‑match tips, and fashion advice. \n Trends delivers a fashion mall experience without the high price tag—making it suitable for shoppers looking stylish yet budget-savvy. </string>
    <string name="pantaloons_description"> Pantaloons blends stylish fashion retail with a personalized shopping experience. The store layout is boutique-like, with clear décor zones for ethnic, casual, and partywear. \n You’ll find carefully curated merchandise ranging from summer florals to formal suits, along with accessories like bags and belts. \n Personalized styling corners and dressing areas enhance the experience. Occasional fashion showcases heighten brand interaction. \n Pantaloons goes beyond basic retail—it’s about nurturing a shopping experience that feels fun, stylish, and approachable. </string>
    <!--  Tourist Places  -->
    <string name="gorakhnath_temple_description"> Gorakhnath Temple is a revered spiritual landmark dedicated to Gorakhnath Maharaj. Surrounded by leafy courtyards, its architecture features domed pavilions and traditional carvings. \n Pilgrims flock here daily, offering prayers in the early morning and evening aarti ceremonies. The atmosphere is alive with chanting, rhythmic bells, and incense. \n Festivals such as Navratri and Guru Purnima turn the temple grounds into a vibrant fair, complete with decorations, music, and local delicacies. \n It\'s not just a religious center—it’s a cultural hub where generations visit to seek blessings, reflect in the peaceful corridors, or witness spiritual traditions firsthand. </string>
    <string name="taramandal_description"> Taramandal is an immersive planetarium and astronomy center that transports visitors through the cosmos. Sleek seating and a domed projection screen create an engaging environment. \n Interactive shows narrate the stories of stars, planets, galaxies, and space missions. Guided sky-gazing sessions help visitors learn constellation navigation. \n Ideal for families and students, the setup often includes tactile models of celestial bodies, making science feel hands-on and exciting. \n Whether you’re curious about black holes or comet tales, Taramandal delivers educational entertainment that sparks wonder across age groups. </string>
    <string name="ramgarh_taal_description"> Ramgarh Taal is a serene retreat made up of over 700 hectares of natural lake, wetlands, and green shoreline. Its calm waters are perfect for boating or enjoying a lakeside evening walk. \n Migratory birds visit during winter months, turning it into an excellent spot for nature photography and birdwatching. The lake is lined with benches and shaded trees for peaceful reflection. \n Local fishermen occasionally glide across the water in traditional boats, adding a cultural nuance to the scenery. \n If you’re seeking fresh air, soothing waterscapes, or natural beauty on a weekend outing, Ramgarh Taal delivers all three in picturesque completeness. </string>
    <string name="nauka_vihar_description"> Nauka Vihar is the boating extension of Ramgarh Taal. Families and couples come to paddle across calm waters in shared paddleboats and small motorboats. \n The waterfront has lined embankments and safety tethers, along with guides who issue life vests and offer short guided tours explaining the lake’s flora and fauna. \n Refreshment stalls nearby serve tea, snacks, and fried treats, perfect after a relaxing boating session. \n A late-afternoon row across the lake, especially during golden hour, turns a simple outing into a poetic lakeside memory. </string>
    <string name="budh_vihar_gate_description"> Budh Vihar Gate marks the entrance to a spiritual community—its striking archway is decorated with sculptural reliefs depicting Buddhist motifs. \n Beyond the gate, you\'ll find public walkways, prayer wheels, and small stone stupas reflecting the peace and mindfulness that the name represents. \n Visitors often pause for mindful meditation or to experience the quiet geometry and balance of semi-public spaces. \n Budh Vihar Gate is less about grand spectacle and more about creating a contemplative, respectful zone for spiritual connection. </string>
    <string name="rail_museum_description"> The local Rail Museum preserves the railway history of the region. Its display includes antique signal lamps, schedules, timetable boards, and miniature models. \n Information panels narrate the arrival of the railways in the region and how they transformed local commerce and mobility. \n A featured highlight is a restored steam engine—an object of fascination for both children and history enthusiasts. \n Though modest in size, the museum is thoughtfully organized. It’s a compelling stop for anyone interested in the story of rail travel and industrial growth. </string>

    <string name="krishna_haveli_location">Golghar, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="sharda_dining_location">Railway Station Road, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="royal_darbar_location">Buxipur, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="tunday_kababi_location">Shahpur, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="terai_location">Betiahata, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="bindas_dhaba_location">Mohanapatti, near NH-29, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="biryani_bay_location">Civil Lines, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="rangrezza_location">Golghar, Gorakhpur</string>

    <string name="ambedkar_park_location">Civil Lines, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="vindyavasini_park_location">Basharatpur, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="nehru_park_location">Golghar, Gorakhpur</string>

    <string name="city_mall_location">Civil Lines, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="orion_mall_location">Rustampur, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="vishal_mega_mart_location">Golghar, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="v_mart_location">Buxipur, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="trends_location">Basharatpur, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="pantaloons_location">City Mall, Gorakhpur</string>

    <string name="gorakhnath_temple_location">Gorakhnath Mandir Road, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="taramandal_location">Planetarium Road, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="ramgarh_taal_location">Lake Road, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="nauka_vihar_location">Ramgarh Taal, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="budh_vihar_gate_location">Budh Vihar Commercial Area, Gorakhpur</string>
    <string name="rail_museum_location">Rail Vihar Colony, Gorakhpur Junction</string>

    <string name="Back_Button">Back Button</string>
    <string name="recommendation_screen">Recommendation Screen</string>
    <string name="place_list_screen">Place List Screen</string>
</resources>